A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Commissioner of the Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1984-1994, 2004-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1984-1994, 2006.
  - 1969-1991 (bulk 1989-1990) (Accession 37349)., 135 cu. ft. (135 boxes)
    - AG Credit and Finance, 1988-1990. (Box 69)
    - Remote Sensing Application, 1989. (Box 70)
    - SLEAC, 1989. (Box 70)
    - Future EPA Programs, 1989. (Box 70)
    - Product/Industry Regulation Division, 1989. (Box 70)
    - Weights and Measures Bureau, 1988-1989. (Box 70)
    - Study of Beneficial Insects, 1989. (Box 70)
    - Racing Gas, 1989. (Box 70)
    - Court Actions, 1989. (Box 70)
    - FIFRA-SFIREG, 1988-1991. (Box 70)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1988-1989. (Box 70)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1987 June. (Box 70)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1987 Mar. (Box 70)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1988. (Box 70)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1987. (Box 70)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1986. (Box 71)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1985. (Box 71)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1989 June. (Box 71)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1988 May. (Box 71)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1989 July. (Box 71)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 1988 Sept. (Box 71)
    - Wine Tour Events, 1988. (Box 71)
    - Appointment calendars, 1981-1983, 1987. (Box 71)
    - Congratulatory letters - reappointment (S. Mason Carbaugh, Commissioner), 1974. (Box 71)
    - Commissioner Carbaugh's reappointment, 1986. (Box 71)
    - Progressive Farmer Man of the Year Award, 1983. (Box 71)
    - Weekly Itineraries for Commissioner Carbaugh, 1988-1989. (Box 71)
    - Agricultural Products Quality and Competitiveness: Now and for the Future - Final Report of the Conference, 1988. (Box 71)
    - NASDA Conference, 1986 Sept. (Box 72)
    - NASDA Board of Directors, 1986 Aug. (Box 72)
    - NASDA Mid-Year Conference, 1986 Mar. (Box 72)
    - NASDA Board of Directors, 1986 Jan. (Box 72)
    - NASDA Board of Directors, 1986. (Box 72)
    - NASDA Mid-Year Conference, 1990 Mar. (Box 72)
    - NASDA, 1990. (Box 72)
    - NASDA, 1989. (Box 72)
    - NASDA Board of Directors, 1989 Mar. (Box 72)
    - NASDA Investments, 1976-1985. (Box 72)
    - NASDA, 1975-1976. (Box 72)
    - Study of Marketing Functions, 1987-1988. (Box 73)
    - Meeting with Cargill-Continental, 1986-1987. (Box 73)
    - Produce Market Managers, 1987. (Box 73)
    - Commodity Commissions (general info), 1985-1987. (Box 73)
    - Virginia Egg Excise Tax, 1986-1987. (Box 73)
    - Wine Marketing Specialist, 1986-1987. (Box 73)
    - Transportation Specialist, 1984-1987. (Box 73)
    - Meeting with Moffett-Spruill, 1987. (Box 73)
    - Farmers Market Board (#4), 1987. (Box 73)
    - Farmers Market Board, 1997 Sept. (Box 73)
    - Planning and Development (Farmer), 19. (Box 73)
    - Use-Value Taxation, 1987-1988. (Box 73)
    - No-Till Day, 1985. (Box 73)
    - Agricultural Opportunities Development (Copeland), 1987-1988. (Box 73)
    - AGriculture and Horticultural Use, 1988. (Box 73)
    - Agricultural and Forestal Districts Act, 1987. (Box 73)
    - Agriculture Finance and Credit (James R. Kee), 1987. (Box 73)
    - Product/Industry Regulation (Southall), 1987. (Box 74)
    - Slowey (Pesticide Complaint), 1987. (Box 74)
    - Cris Hardy Livestock, Inc., 1987. (Box 74)
    - W/M Scale Testing Program, 1987. (Box 74)
    - Duer hearing, 1987. (Box 74)
    - Weights and Measures Inspector Regrade, 1986-1987. (Box 74)
    - Weights and Measures Week, 1987. (Box 74)
    - Gypsy Moth, 1987-1988. (Box 74)
    - SECURE (Risk Retention), 1987-1988. (Box 74)
    - Meeting with Sam Rosenthal, 1987. (Box 74)
    - VDACS Legislation, 1987. (Box 74)
    - Proposals, 1984. (Box 74)
    - House Document 8 - Milk Inspection, 1985. (Box 74)
    - HB 1714, 1985. (Box 74)
    - Budget Amendments, 1988. (Box 74)
    - Annual Reports, 1981-1982. (Box 74)
  - 1994, 2004 (Accession 43628)., 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes)
    This accession is arranged in no discernable order.
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 1994. (Box 1)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994. (Box 1)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994. (Box 1)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Blankenship, Donald, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Commissioner's Office - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Memos - SMT, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Dickenson, William P., 1994. (Box 2)
    - Adams, Sandra, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Administrative and Financial Services, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Development Services, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Farmland Preservation, Office of, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Jackson, Karen E., 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - HRO, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Internal Auditor, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Seward, Roy E., 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy Planning and Research, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Giles, Perida, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Stewardship, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Lidholm, Elaine, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Communications and Promotion, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Alvarez, Andy - Consumer Affairs, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Consumer Affairs - Annual Report, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Fulgham, Frank - Office of Plant and Pest Services, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Endangered Species, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Lawson, Marvin - Consumer Protection, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Protection, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Animal and Food Industry Services, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Correspondence/Financials (M. Craig Halbleib and Donald Blankenship), 1994. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Information Systems, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Garey, Louis, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Martin, Teddy, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Procurement, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Cardin, David, Dr., 1994. (Box 3)
    - Bulls, Donald, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Pesticides, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Metolachlor, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Rogers, Alan - Office of Product and Industry Standards, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Weights and Measures - Legisltive proposals, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Weights and Measures - Impact of Reduction, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Dairy and Food, Office of, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Food Security - Dairy, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Sleight, Thomas, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Division of Marketing, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Accounts, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Agendas - SMT, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Agricultural Spraying - Best Practices, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Amendments - General Assembly, 1994. (Box 3)
    - ABC Board, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Amendments - Governor, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Apple Board, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Attorney General, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Avian Influenza, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Awards and Recognition - VDACS, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Awards Committee - VDACS, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Black Farmers Association, National, 1994. (Box 3)
    - BSE, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Cattle Grading fees, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Chippokes Plantation Farm Foundation, 1994. (Box 3)
    - CVC, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Commodity Boards, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Commission on Local Government, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Continuity of Operations Plan, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance Office, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Council of State Governments, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Coyotes, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Dairy Compact, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Dairymen's Association of Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Delegates, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Delmarva Poultry, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Disposal Agreement AI, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Disasters, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1994. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Equine Industry Study, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Farmland and Forest Land Preservation - Annual Report, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Emerald Ash Borer, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Farmer's Market System Report, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Food Policy Council, 1994. (Box 4)
    - FOIA, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Governor's Office, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Health Dept., 1994. (Box 4)
    - Homeland Security, 1994. (Box 4)
    - House Council - Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - H. J. Resolution No. 228, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Human Resources Management, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Information Technology Agency, Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Interior, U. S. Dept. of the, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Information Management, Council on, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Invasive Species Work Group, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Hot Case, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Housing and Community Development, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Land Use, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Library of Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Legislative guidelines, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Legislative Services, Div. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Legislation, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Milk, Raw - Sale of - Cow Sharing, 1994. (Box 4)
    - MOU to Control Tropical Soda Apple, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Milk Commission, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Natural Resources, Secretary of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Perdue, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Pilgrims Pride, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Pork Industry Association, Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Poultry Growers Cooperative, Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Procurement Management - Review Report, 1994. (Box 4)
    - S. J. Resolution No. 57, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Senators, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Soil and Water Conservation, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Sole Source, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Solem, Christine, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Security Position - Agricultural, 1994. (Box 4)
    - VDACS Reports to the General Assembly, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Eastern Shore Agriculture Conference and Trade Show, 1994 Jan 6-7. (Box 5)
    - Colonial Soil and Water Conservation District, 2004. (Box 5)
    - VITA - Medium and Large Agency Transition Workshop, 2004. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board meeting, 2004 Jan 15. (Box 5)
    - Agency Head meeting, 2004. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Grown Conference and Trade Show, 2004 Jan 21-23. (Box 5)
    - Carolina/Virginia Dairy Products Association, 2004 Jan 27. (Box 5)
    - Virginia State Dairymen's Association - Meeting, 2004 Jan 20. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Soybean Association - Winter Conference, 2004 Feb 6. (Box 5)
    - Virginia State Feed Association - Annual Conference, 2004 Feb 25-26. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Cotton Economics - Annual Meeting, 2004 Feb 10. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Beef Industry Council - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 Feb 17. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Food and Beverage Association - Annual Meeting, 2004 Mar 15-16. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council - Board Meeting, 2004 Mar 22. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Wine Board Transition Task Force, 2004 Apr 6. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 Apr 8. (Box 5)
    - virginia Poultry Health and Management Seminar, 2004 Apr 13. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2004 Apr 15. (Box 5)
    - VEIAA - Meeting, 2004 Apr 29. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Small Grains Association - Field Day, 2004 May 20. (Box 5)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee - Meeting, 2004 May 12. (Box 5)
    - Forestry Expo, 2004 June 4. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Forage and Grassland Council - Conference, 2004 June 12-16. (Box 5)
    - VEIAA - Spring Conference, 2004 June 23. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2004 July 15. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Cattlemen Conference, 2004 July 16. (Box 5)
    - Emergency Support Work Group Training, 2004 July 8. (Box 5)
    - AG Expo - Eastern Shore, 2004 Aug 12. (Box 5)
    - State Fair of Virginia Wine Competition, 2004 Aug 16. (Box 5)
    - Harrisonburg AI Meeting, 2004 Aug 18. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Wine Board - Meeting, 2004 Aug 23. (Box 5)
    - Virginia State University - Agriculture Field Day, 2004 Aug 24. (Box 5)
    - UVLA Field Day, 2004 Sept 1. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 Sept 23. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2004 Oct 14. (Box 5)
    - VDACS Regional Service Awards, 2004. (Box 5)
    - Farmers Market System Operations - Meeting, 2004 Nov 9. (Box 5)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee - Meeting, 2004 Nov 3. (Box 5)
    - VEIAA - Fall Conference, 2004 Oct 27. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council - State Policy and Development Committee, 2004 Nov 12. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation - Annual meeting, 2004 Nov 29. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2004 Mar 18. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2004 June 10. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2004 Sep 24. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2004 Dec 9. (Box 5)
    - Scorecard - Governor's Management Standard Executive Agreement, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Secretary of Administration, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Racing Fuels Register, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Southern States, 2004. (Box 6)
    - State Fair, 2004. (Box 6)
    - States Ratification Committee, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Southeastern Virginia Farmers Market Coop, 2004. (Box 6)
    - State Police, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004-2006. (Box 6)
    - Strategic Plan, 2002-2004. (Box 6)
    - Task Force - Agriculture, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Task Force - Equine Study, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Task Force - Food Safety, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco - Burley Tobacco Warehouse, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco - Tobacco Trust Certification Board, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco - National Tobacco Grower Settlement Trust, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Tobacco - Minutes of the Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Treasury, Dept. of, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Syngenta Crop Protection, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia State University History Project - African American Contributions, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Tech, 2004. (Box 6)
    - USDA, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Results, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Works, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Legislative tracking, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board, 2004. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Wine Board Transition Task Force - Governor's Wine Study Work Group, 2004. (Box 7)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA), 2004. (Box 7)
    - Southern Trade Association (SUSTA), 2004. (Box 7)
    - Vanderwoude, Hill and Hill v. VDACS, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Suggested Reponses, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board, 2004. (Box 7)
    - Wine Board Reduction, 2004. (Box 7)
  - 2005 (Accession 44118)., 9 cu. ft. (9 boxes)
    - Weekly reports to the Secretary, 2005. (Box 1)
    - Issues Briefing - Short-term, to Secretary Bloxom, 2005 Jan. (Box 1)
    - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry (1), 2005 Jan-July. (Box 1)
    - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry (2), 2005 July-Dec. (Box 1)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (1), 2005 Jan-Feb. (Box 1)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (2), 2005 Feb-June. (Box 1)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (3), 2005 June-July. (Box 1)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (4), 2005 July-Aug. (Box 1)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (5), 2005 Aug-Oct. (Box 1)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (6), 2005 Oct-Nov. (Box 1)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (7), 2005 Oct-Nov. (Box 2)
    - Courter, J. Carlton, III (8), 2005 Oct-Dec. (Box 2)
    - Blankenship, Donald G. (1), 2005. (Box 2)
    - Mulugeta, Marsko, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Butts, Donald W., 2005. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Commissioner's Office, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Dickenson, William P., 2005. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Development Services, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Memos - SMT, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Jackson, Karen E., 2005. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resources, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Internal Auditor, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Seward. Roy E., 2005. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy, Planning and Development, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Agricultural Stewardship, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Lidholm, Elaine, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Communication and Media Relations, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Adams, Sandra, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Administration and Financial Services, 2005. (Box 2)
    - Halbleib, M. Craig (3), 2005 June-Dec. (Box 2)
    - Halblieb, M. Craig (2), 2005 Feb-June. (Box 2)
    - Halblieb, M. Craig (1), 2005 Feb-June. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous Procurement, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Animal and Food Industry Services, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Wilkes, Richard L., 2005. (Box 3)
    - Cardin, David 2005. (Box 3)
    - Dairy and Foods Office, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Poultry Distributor Application, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Poultry Litter and Animal Manure - Chesapeake Bay, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Alvarez, Andy, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Protection, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Consumer Affairs Office, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Consumer Affairs - Annual Report, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Plant and Pest Services Office, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Coyote Damage Control Program - Virginia, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Emerald Ash Borer, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Pesticide (1), 2005 Jan-Feb. (Box 3)
    - Pesticide (2), 2005 Feb-June. (Box 3)
    - Pesticide (3), 2005 June. (Box 3)
    - Pesticide (4), 2005 July-Dec. (Box 3)
    - Pesticide (5), 2005 Dec. (Box 3)
    - Weights and Measures - Office Audit, 2005. (Box 3)
    - Weights and Measures - Inspections, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Weights and Measures - Annual Report, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Weights and Measures - Plan for Funding Report, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Vulture Damage, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous - Division of Marketing, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Sleight, Thomas, 2005. (Box 4)
    - International Trade Office, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Grain Marketing Inspection Fee, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Peanut Inspection Fee Schedule, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Accounts, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Agenda - SMT, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Agreement between VDACS and DCLS, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Agreement - Farmers Markets Nutrition Program, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Agreement - VADACS and VDOT, 2005. (Box 4)
    - MOU between VDACS and MD Dept. of Agriculture, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Agreement between VDACS and USDA (APHIS) and Wildlife Services, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Memo Agreement between VDACS and Virginia Beach, 2005. (Box 4)
    - MOU between VDACS and DCLS, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Agriculture and Forestry Export Strategy Task Force, 2005. (Box 4)
    - MOU Shore to Store Program, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Agricultural Enterprise Act Report, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Agricultural History Report, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Apple Board, Virginia, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Attorney General's Office, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Audit - Seed Laboratory, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Avian Influenza, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Awards Committee - VDACS, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Biodiesel Fuel Report to Governor and General Assembly, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Briefing Issues Analysis - VDACS, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Code Commission, Virginia, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC), 2005. (Box 4)
    - Commission on Local Government, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Continuity of Operations Plan (COOP), 2005. (Box 4)
    - Council of State Governments, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Daily Compact, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Dairy Regulation letter, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Dairymen's Association, Virginia, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Delmarva Poultry, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Delegates, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Disasters, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Education Organization, Virginia, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, US (1), 2005. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, US (2), 2005. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Equine Industry Study Report, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Farmers Market Board, Virginia, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Farm Bureau Federation, Virginia, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Foundation for Agriculture, Innovation and Rural Sustainability, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Freedom of Information, 2005. (Box 4)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Governor's Office, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Health, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Homeland Security Exercise Plan, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Horse Center, Virginia, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Horse Council, Virginia, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Hot Line, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Information Technology Agency (VITA), 2005. (Box 5)
    - Interior, US Dept. of, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Interstate Pest Control Compact - Annual Report, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Interstate Pest Control Compact, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Invasive Species Workgroup, Virginia, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 2005. (Box 5)
    - Land Use, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Legislative Guidelines, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Library of Virginia, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Mandates, Federal, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Managing Virginia Program (MVP), 2005. (Box 5)
    - MOU - Shore to Store and Custom Pak, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Performance Measures, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Poultry Litter, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Risk Management, Div. - DGS, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Scorecard - Governor's Management, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Senators, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Sole Source, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Solem, Christine (Goat Milk), 2005. (Box 5)
    - Southern Virginia Farmers Market Coop, 2005. (Box 5)
    - State Fair, 2005. (Box 5)
    - State Police, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 5)
    - States Ratification Committee, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Study Reports, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Tenure Agreement, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Tobacco Acreage, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Tobacco Grower Settlement Trust, National, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Tobacco Trust Certification Board, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Turner, Clinton, Dr., 2005. (Box 5)
    - Transportation Dept. of, 2005. (Box 5)
    - USDA (1), 2005. (Box 5)
    - USDA (2), 2005. (Box 5)
    - VPI and SU, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Virginia State University, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Virginia State University - History Project - African-American Contributions, 2005. (Box 5)
    - YMCA, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board, 2005. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Wine Board, 2005. (Box 5)
    - NASDA, 2005. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation, 2005. (Box 6)
    - SASDA, 2005. (Box 6)